Jonas Walden

Address: Ocala, Fl

Phone: (352)-288-8646 | Email: smodcartoon@gmail.com

LinkedIn- https://www.linkedin.com/in/

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Professional results driven and passionate Front End Developer with over 2 years of experience in building and designing websites and web applications trained in full stack Web Development. Seeking Web Developer position with a company who values and has a desire to improve and update their web development department.

#Skills

















Front-End

HTML5/ CSS3 / Sass /Less Javascript ES6 / React.js

Back End

REST / Node.js mongoose Express.js

Source Control

Git(Git Flow) SCRUM / Agile Github/Bitbucket

FrameWorks

React / Redux Hooks/Spring Context API

UI/UX

Wireframing / Balsamiq/Figma PhotoShop/Illustrator

#Projects

UnBlush Unblush May 2019 -

- Link To Project => https://awk-dating.firebaseapp.com/
- Full Stack Dating app built with Firebase, React.js ,Hooks,Spring and the Context API.
- Built in 5 weeks this was my capstone project for Lambda School that passed a third party code review and a capstone defence process conducted by Lambda School instructors and students.
- ▶Implemented Travis for CI/CD for continuous deployment Github as source control and hosted on firebase.
- Designed and built matching algorithm to match users with potential mates .



Pokemon PokeDex March 2019

Link to Project => https://priceless-albattani-5d7132.netlify.com/

- Full stack web app using Express.js React.js , Redux, mongoDB and deployed to Heroku using Github CI/CD.
- Later This project uses a pokemon api to gather sort and deliver data on hundreds of Pokemon with fuzzy search and state management.
- Using a github organization this project was built in a agile work environment using trello cards and feature by feature rollout methodology.



TipsEase February 2019 -

Link to project => https://competent-goldwasser-ec1394.netlify.com/

- A React.js full stack web app that uses Express.js for the backend and Sqlite3 for the database.
- Independently using Stripe payment api and a robust UI.
- Git was used as the source control for this project and Github was used for continuous deployment to netlify servers where it is hosted.
- JSON Web Tokens were used for authentication and the backend is hosted on heroku.

All code for projects available on my Github https://github.com/UnknownMonk

#Education

Lambda School/ FullStack Web Development / Jan 2019 30 week immersive code bootcamp with 40 hour weeks covering Computer Science, Algorithms, Web Development and Simulated work environments. 7 1/2 months of training on Html,Css,Preprocessors, JavaScript,React.js,Express.js,Testing Source Control and problem solving training.

#Professional Experience

S_{*}T_{*}A_{*}R_{*}S Specialty Transportation and Regulatory Services (STARS)

October 2018 - Present : Ocala, Fl

- ▶ Responsible for SEO, Optimizing speed and performance overall look and feel of the website.
- Adding user membership and front end redesign .
- Implemented and added UI features for a smoother user experience.
- Integrating a e-learning platform and custom e-commerce platform.



Ken Jones Real Estate School LLC / Web Developer/ Ui/Ux Designer

July 2018 - November 2018: Ocala, Fl

- ▶ Custom website built with Sass precompiler flexbox Javascript and HTML5.
- ▶ Coordinated closely with owner to develop UI/UX, Design, and QA. Prototype and WireFrame.
- Implemented a method to create a strong email list using php forms and javascript
- Interface with the PayPal API to handle payments and refunds.



Koksmif LLC / Web Developer/ Ui/Ux Designer

August 2015 - December 2017: Auburn, Ca

- Managed day to day operations including screen printing, Graphic Design, responsible for designing and building the E-commerce website
- Interfaced with the Stripe API to handle credit card payments of online orders.
- Implemented new UI and templating system with Bootstrap and JavaScript to improve UX and system flexibility.
- Managed day to day operations including screen printing, Graphic design
- ▶Updated legacy code to streamline the signup forms and emailing systems.